Better get in there, Suzuka is waiting so I'll catch you late. Sound good?
Sure thing.
I'm afraid I may have gotten here too early.
I beat Akira. I wonder what he's like.
I can't wait to see.
I'm afraid I may have gotten here too early.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
踊る風に誘われた坂道の向こう側に
どこまでも広がる青
目を奪われて
音を立て
ときめきの予感
真っ白な秘めた気持ちが色づいてゆく
最後は君と紡いでく未来
今はまだ手探りで迷っても
本物で描き出す光
七色の明日が呼んでる
道しぬって
楽だって
不安くなれ
分け合って
君がいる
いつだって
ほら笑って
終わりでも
あた SEE
大好きや
笑ってる
retailers
忽々づいて
サンガーアーメン
カリン
冗入
ディ Sun
ビピューハポテ
テ Myth
I feel pro! I'm a fan! It's just the greatest, huh?
How weird.
Omni is running a little late.
Hope he's okay.
He says he's done changing, so it's not bad.
Oh, thank you so much!
Next, could you try out her pose from Tanabata Fest?
Sure.
CUTINESS OVERLOAD!
You look perfect! Seriously, thank you!
What do I do? I'm trapped.
I was on my way to meet up with Maureen.
Excuse me.
And I got held up.
I only meant to take a few.
And then came the line.
Now I'm totally stuck.
Thanks again for the pics!
And thank you for taking them.
I'm so late.
I'd like some photos, please.
Of course.
How goes it?
You cutie pie, you.
Hey, Maureen.
It's a good thing my butt came looking for you.
This line is wild.
I'm super sorry.
I didn't account for this.
Nah, chill.
You...
You look frickin' adorable as Hokuto Neon.
You nailed the skirt.
I almost forgot the elite class uniforms have that sick universe pattern.
Also, the mole and the fang are total perfection.
Thanks.
It's my first time wearing a fang.
At work, Hokuto Neon isn't the type of idol to show much emotion.
But when she flipped off that annoying fan who was heckling her manager, I instantly became a fan.
I know, right?
I have mad respect for dudes like you who are drawn to a strong but silent girly.
Hang on.
Is that your new camera?
You mean this old thing?
I'm jealous.
Maybe I should buy one.
You could be triplets with me and Suzuka.
Right?
Cute, huh?
Duuuude!
That's actually a boy?!
Holy freaking shit!
I'm so happy to be alive!
Thank you times a million, Marine!
He's so nice to meet you.
Sorry I was late.
I want to photograph every centimeter of his body.
But on the other hand, I don't want to get arrested.
Curve attack, curve attack.
Why do I channel this?
I have witnessed the most immaculate cross-dressing I've ever seen in my entire life
and the only way I can think to express my gratitude is with honey.
So, do you take credit cards?
Suzuka, you freak.
People!
Next time you draw a crowd, just say you need to cut off the line.
Cut off the line?
If your line ever gets too lengthy, go up to the very last photographer and politely ask them to cut it off for you.
Then they'll turn around and tell any other photographers that the cosplayer has already decided to cut their cue.
I didn't know there was such a simple solution.
What I hoped!
I can cut off this line.
Thank you very much.
You ready?
Look over here!
About my pose, any ideas?
I get to pick!
You're an angel for that!
Uhhh…
You should do the Venus Mew Dream pose from the chorus!
I love it!
That's such a cute one!
Here we go!
Dangerous!
Hey, you asked for this!
My new fave idol!
I'll go to all your shows!
Take the picture for you!
Well, he's definitely a boy when he laughs!
Thanks so much for the photo!
And thank you for your helpful advice!
You're a lifesaver!
Great job!
You killed it, just like you always do!
You're too sweet to me!
Hey, could Wakana not make this one?
No, he's here!
He's busy meeting up with some prop maker!
How interesting!
I came with a couple of my cosplay friends too!
One is in full costume right now, and the other makes awesome props!
Awesome…
Thanks so much for the photo!
And thank you for your helpful advice!
You're a lifesaver!
Great job!
You killed it, just like you always do!
You're too sweet to me!
Hey, could Wakana not make this one?
No, he's here!
He's busy meeting up with some prop maker!
How interesting!
I came with a couple of my cosplay friends too!
One is in full costume right now, and the other makes awesome props!
Oh, that's all right!
He's a cute little girl!
Yeah!
Awesome props. She's meeting up with this high school girl who's a big fan of hers.
Nice! It's from Akira!
A dragon jacket.
He'll be here any minute!
Alright, now I just need to find the dragon.
That...sure looks like a dragon.
Is that a Samui?
Ha! I, uh, are you Akira?
You're the high school girl?
Dude?
Cute! I've seen that anime before.
This dreamboat is my friend, Mia!
Oh, hey there.
Are you seriously cosplaying Reno-Q from Double Clutch right now?!
It's a pretty old manga, so I'm shocked you know it. I'm glad some high schoolers appreciate the classics.
I've read all the manga, watched the anime, and even watched the movie!
Narokami-hai, sign me up yesterday!
All the characters are so sexy! The fan service in that series is servicing, and I am thankful!
I don't remember any fan service.
Your features are so chiseled!
Your face is a work of art!
That's right. It's my art. I just painted it.
Say what?!
My natural features are pretty round, so I wear lots of makeup to look more angular.
I wash my face, and boom, I'm a stranger!
Same goes for me. It's so fun to swap out your face for a new one!
And swap out your hair!
I think that your favorite things to swap are your genders!
Miyako, do you care if I snap some pics?
Go for it!
Yay! Thanks so much!
I'm ready.
Sweet!
Looking good!
Dreamy!
Wow, you look handsome!
Thanks for your time!
Yeah, no prob at all.
Now it's my turn!
Huh?
Hey, why do you crouch down for pics?
Because it can really take your photos to the next level.
Watch and learn.
Huh?
If I take it from my normal sight line,
I get this.
Right, she looks hot.
Just wait.
Huh?
If you take it from this angle...
It's totally different!
Yep!
It's the exact same pose, but her legs look longer.
Small.
And her face, it looks a little bit smaller.
Come to think of it, at the photoshoot for Blaze, Shinju crouched down for a bunch of pics.
When I shot Amane, I was going for cuteness, so I angled myself above him and had him look up at my camera.
Playing with angles can be super fun. Useful, too.
For sure.
Now that I know, I've gotta try more shots.
I wanted to ask, do you two have any big plans after this?
Huh?
If you're both free...
We should hang.
You down?
Ma'am, I am so terribly sorry!
I assumed from your name and photo online that you were a gentleman.
It's an easy mistake, to be honest.
I thought you were a girl.
Sorry.
May I ask why?
I'm pretty sure I referred to myself as a guy.
Maybe so, but that term is super neutral.
The same thing goes for girl, too.
Guess I wasn't aware.
Thinking back, Usami has said...
Us girls.
And I sort of remember this saying...
Us guys!
Interesting.
I guess those words can correspond to a moment or feeling instead of a gender.
Us girls!
Tell me, where'd the Wakana handle come from, anyway?
Favorite character?
No, it's my name.
It's a nice name.
That makes sense.
I use my real name, too.
Agira.
We have something in common, then.
Yeah.
Right away.
I wanted to ask about this.
See?
It's an amazing cosplay.
But what series is the character from?
I tried to find it, but I didn't have any luck.
Yeah, because it's not from a series.
Huh?
It's mine.
A random OC.
Aoi's...
Let's learn about cosplay!
Thank you for joining me today!
You don't know me, but I'm Suzuka's friend, Aoi.
When cosplaying, you must first focus on the special character that you're with.
One option is to choose someone from a pre-existing series.
Copyright costs.
You could also cosplay as a specific occupation.
Or perhaps, you would prefer to cosplay your own OC,
an original character you concoct in your very own mind.
So creative!
For example, Agira dreamt up this rugged ranger all on her own.
Isn't that cool?
Awesome!
I've never heard of an OC.
That's so unique!
You like to do this?
Yeah!
I've never heard of an OC.
That's so unique!
You like traditional designs?
Yeah, and stuff that's usually catered toward men.
How neat!
I appreciate the praise, but calm down.
My cosplay isn't particularly unique or impressive.
I like traditional Japanese art and patterns,
and I'm into swords.
It's practically been done to death.
It's not really that creative.
What?!
What's up?
I'm sorry.
It was rude of me to raise my voice at you like that.
It's fine.
Fine!
What you're saying might be true,
but that doesn't make your art any less impressive!
That's why I reached out to you!
To me, it's no less than perfect!
When I said what you're saying might be true,
I meant in the way that I don't really know what I'm talking about,
so I defer to your expertise.
I wasn't trying to double down on your criticism.
It's okay.
Yeah, I get that.
Thank you.
Sure, of course.
So you want to learn about prop-making, don't you?
Let's get to it, then.
I'm very thankful.
To start, there are a few comments I didn't send.
You have more?
Uh-huh.
You sent so many.
That's a crazy word count.
But I'm here because I was impressed by your attention to detail,
so I suppose I should have expected this.
That was half of what I wrote!
Just wait!
Like I was saying before,
the detail you captured in the blade was seriously un-
It's fine.
Um, so sorry.
It's Gojo.
I'm aware.
Where you at?
I'm on the same bench where we chatted with Himeno.
Nice.
We're close.
Can Suzuka and I swing by?
Uh, give me just a moment.
Hey, so, I actually came by here with a friend today.
And they want to meet up?
That's fine.
Oh, thank you so much!
Come on by!
Will do.
I already found you.
Ha-ha!
I'm over here!
Hiya, Goober!
Look up!
See me now?
Hey!
I've got some super fun news!
Get ready, get ready!
You ready?
Suzuka's sexy friends invited me to their after party,
and even told me I could bring a buddy!
A party?
Uh-huh!
Apparently they threw shindigs after all these events.
Fun!
Huh?
Oh, hey, I forgot to introduce you to Kitagawa.
This is Akira.
You're Akira?
Hey down there!
How goes it?
My name's Maureen.
Uh, hello?
What the?
Aki?!
Oh, hey, girly pop!
Wait, is this the prop maker friend you were telling me about?
That's like a level 10 crazy coincidence!
Yeah!
This is him.
Meet Gojo.
Huh?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Wakana Gojo.
You are?
I think of Wakana as a woman's name,
so I totally thought he was a girl.
I see now I was mistaken.
He's Akira's fan and Maureen's friend.
That can only mean one thing.
I've spotted a real-life high school boy in the wild!
Goo goo gaga, baby!
I'm Maureen's mature lady friend!
Huh?
That wasn't normal!
I wonder if Amine and Miyako have wrapped up yet?
I've never been to an after-party before,
so I'm mega hyped!
So am I!
Mia!
Emergency!
This after-party is risky!
Aki and Maureen!
This is bad!
I loved the look,
but I feel so much better without all the tape!
Do you always hold mini-parties after cosplay events?
Always?
Let's learn about cosplay!
Hi, it's Aoi again!
Have you ever been to a party after a cosplay event?
They're one of my favorite parts of the day!
You see, though events are fun, they can be stressful.
There's so much to look at and so many pictures to pose for,
you might not have time to talk to your friends!
That's why it's best to go somewhere you can chat,
like a karaoke room, restaurant, or collab cafe!
Whenever we get really sweaty, we celebrate at the spa!
How fancy!
The spa?
I have to show you Miyako's epic rindo cute!
I'd love to see it!
Ta-da!
What an awesome shot!
I got a better one!
Check it!
Suzuka shared all her photographer magic with me!
She looks completely different there!
I know!
Insane, right?
Absolutely!
I didn't realize adjusting the angle could do so much!
Sounds good!
Let's pick a few more things to share!
Let's play with that next photo shoot!
Yeah, for sure!
Dang, that was speedy!
How pretty!
Akira, could you grab my bag?
Here.
Thank you!
Huh?
Your baby rindo knew he is so cute and squishy!
I thought he could really amplify my pancake pic!
So adults walk around with dolls too?
Not a thought!
And she's talking to it!
I'm planning to sew you a beautiful new outfit today!
And then tomorrow, it'll finally be ready for you to try on!
So it's not just me!
I'm obsessed with its tiny costume!
I decorated my Xi'an Nui too!
Yeah!
I think you posted a pic of it!
The outfit is one of my favorites!
Then why are you gripping the poor thing like a baseball?
I used to keep her on my bag, but I suck at taking care of my stuff.
Now my Nui sit by my TV at home, so they can't get all nasty.
You bring your dolls with you sometimes too, right?
It would be a crime not to!
Agreed!
It's always nice to have a version of your fave!
And you feel like you're about to kill someone at work.
Seeing it brings you peace of mind!
Yeah!
I don't think Ojo caught that.
Oh, he's not gonna make it either.
That's too bad.
Is everything okay?
We had a fun group cosplay planned out for next Sunday.
But all the other cosplayers had to drop out because they're needed at their jobs.
It would be such a bummer not to get weekends off.
We already reserved the studio, so maybe just the three of us should go.
It's better than nothing.
What are you guys cosplaying?
Played Coffin?
We're doing that.
Coffin?
I'm obsessed with it right now.
It's so frickin' awesome!
I'll need those pics!
Uh...
Huh?
What's Coffin?
A horror game!
It's about these cute nuns who live together and slowly get killed off one by one.
The goal of the game is to figure out who killed them.
So it's a mystery game.
There's Sister Mira, Sister Rose, Sister Char, Sister Emma, Sister Claire, and Sister Soph.
You're still looking for people, right?
So, uh, may I join your group?
You want to?
A habit would hide my physique and I'm a really big fan of the game.
You're the best ever!
I'm begging you to let me give you money!
Thank you!
You're saving our lives!
I'm just happy that you're letting me join!
Did you make the outfits?
Nope, they're pre-made.
They sell them at ACOS.
So they'll probably have the character wigs, too.
I'll buy one today.
Oh!
They're cheap?
Today?
So proactive!
Now you only need three more people.
You should join, Maureen.
You are a Coffin fan, right?
I am, but...
You have to do it!
I was just thinking about how I want to cosplay with you again.
Would that be okay?
That would be great, as long as Maureen doesn't mind!
Yeah!
If you're free, you should do it!
Well, I would.
But, uh...
I'm actually on a diet at the moment.
I can't do any new cosplays right now.
Ah, that explains your unsweet tea and the salad.
Also, that's a real quick turnaround.
Nah, we couldn't get it ready in time.
Then you should buy a pre-made costume like the rest of us.
Oh...
Since we're a group, the matching outfits will look cohesive.
We would love to have you if you're willing to join us.
Hmm?
Sounds like a good plan.
I'm so down!
Your girl Maureen is putting the inn in Coffin!
We really appreciate it!
This is gonna be gnarly!
What a huge win!
Just two members away from the full party!
This rocks!
I love group cosplays!
Oh, I know!
Question!
Hmm?
Is it cool if I invite somebody, too?
Of course it is!
You're the best!
I'll call her later!
It's fine, just call her now!
Well, if you insist...
She's calling someone.
Who could it be?
Is it really?
Is it someone scary?
No, that's not it.
She's just a very particular person.
Getting her to agree could be a challenge.
It's Maureen!
Hey, Juju!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What do you want?
Kawaii, kaiwaii!
鏡の中の 笑顔の私
昨日とは違う 輝いてる
ドキドキしてるこの気持ちは 君に伝えたい電気のハートも 新しい服で 新しい私 心も着替えて ニューニューニュー
かわいい界隈 トキメキ感じて 君からの変身まで かわいい界隈 胸も高鳴る 雨変わるよ 君と変わるよ
かわいい界隈
次回